foxsportsasia.com 2019-09-10

# Privacy Policy | FOX Sports Asia

**PRIVACY POLICY**

The Walt Disney Company has acquired certain 21st Century Fox businesses, including those providing the services described below. This policy has been updated to reflect that transaction.

Date: March 2019

**Table of Contents:**

  1. [INTRODUCTION](http://www.natgeotv.com.au/about/privacy.aspx#1)
  2. [COLLECTION OF INFORMATION](http://www.natgeotv.com.au/about/privacy.aspx#2)
  3. [USE AND DISCLOSURE](http://www.natgeotv.com.au/about/privacy.aspx#3)
  4. [SECURITY](http://www.natgeotv.com.au/about/privacy.aspx#4)
  5. [USER ACCESS AND CONTROL](http://www.natgeotv.com.au/about/privacy.aspx#5)
  6. [OTHER IMPORTANT INFORMATION](http://www.natgeotv.com.au/about/privacy.aspx#6)
  7. [CONTACT DETAILS AND COMPLAINTS HANDLING](http://www.natgeotv.com.au/about/privacy.aspx#7)  

FOX Networks Group Singapore Pte. Ltd. (“ **we** ” or “ **FNG** “) is committed to responsible privacy practices and to complying with the privacy principles contained in the Personal Data Protection Act 2012 (No. 26 of 2012) (“ **PDPA** “) and wants you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose information from and about you. This Privacy Policy describes our practices in connection with information collected through services such as websites, mobile sites, applications (“ **apps** “), and widgets (collectively, the “ **FNG Services** “). By using FNG Services, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. As described more fully below, we share certain information with our company affiliates.  Our company affiliates include members of [The Walt Disney Family of Companies](https://privacy.thewaltdisneycompany.com/en/definitions) (https://privacy.thewaltdisneycompany.com/en/definitions) (“ **Company Affiliates** ”). For further information on Company Affiliates please contact [privacycontact@disney.com](mailto:privacycontact@disney.com). 

This Privacy Policy applies to all users, including both those who use the FNG Services without being registered with or subscribing to a FNG Service and those who have registered with or subscribed to a FNG Service. This Privacy Policy applies to FNG’s collection and use of your personal information.

  1. ﻿ **COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**

FNG and our service providers may collect the following information from and about you:

**Registration Information** is the information you submit to register for a FNG Service, for example, to create an account, post comments, receive a newsletter, or enter a contest or sweepstakes. Registration Information may include, for example, name, email address, gender, zip code and birthday.

**Public Information and Posts** consist of comments or content that you post to the FNG Services and the information about you that accompanies those posts or content, which may include a name, user name, comments, likes, status, profile information and picture. Public Information and Posts are always public, which means they are available to everyone and may be displayed in search results on external search engines.

**Social Media Information and Content**. If you access or log-in to a FNG Service through a third party social media service or another website, app, service or log-in (“Other Service”), or connect a FNG Service to Other Services, the information we collect may also include your user ID and/or user name associated with that Other Service, any information or content you have permitted the Other Service to share with us, such as your profile picture, email address or friends’ lists, and any information you have made public in connection with that Other Service (collectively, “Social Media Information and Content”). When you access the FNG Services through Other Services, or when you connect a FNG Service to Other Services, you are authorizing FNG to collect, store, and use any and all Social Media Information and Content in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Authenticated Content**.  To access certain video content via the FNG Services, you may be redirected to your television content provider’s registration page where you will be required to register directly with your television content provider.  Please contact your television content provider directly for questions on your account, including how to access or cancel your account.  Any information that you provide to your television content provider will be subject to the applicable television content provider’s privacy policy, rather than this Privacy Policy.  We have no control over, and are not responsible for, any television content provider’s use of information collected via the FNG Services.

**Activity Information.** When you access and interact with the FNG Services, we may collect certain information about those visits. For example, in order to permit your connection to the FNG Services, our servers receive and record information about your computer, device, and browser, including potentially your IP address, browser type, and other software or hardware information. If you access the FNG Services from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device, geolocation data, or other transactional information for that device.

Cookies and other tracking technologies (such as browser cookies, pixels, beacons, and Adobe Flash technology including cookies) are comprised of small bits of data that often include a de-identified or anonymous unique identifier. Websites, apps and other services send this data to your browser when you first request a web page and then store the data on your device so the website can access information when you make subsequent requests for pages from that service. These technologies may also be used to collect and store information about your usage of the FNG Services, such as pages you have visited, content you have viewed, search queries you have run and advertisements you have seen.

Third parties that support the FNG Services by serving advertisements or providing services, such as allowing you to share content or tracking aggregate FNG Services usage statistics, may also use these technologies to collect similar information. FNG does not control these third-party technologies and their use is governed by the privacy policies of third parties using such technologies. For more information about third-party advertising networks and similar entities that use these technologies, see [www.aboutads.info/consumers](http://www.aboutads.info/consumers), and to opt-out of such ad networks’ and services’ advertising practices, go to [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information. Users can manage the use of Flash technologies, with the Flash management tools available at Adobe’s website, see <http://www.adobe.com/security/flashplayer/>. Please note that by blocking any or all cookies you may not have access to certain features, content or personalization available through the FNG Services.

**Information from Other Sources**. We may supplement the information we collect with information from other sources, such as publicly available information from social media services, commercially available sources and information from our Company Affiliates or business partners in Singapore or internationally.

  1. **USE AND DISCLOSURE**

**PURPOSE OF COLLECTION**

We use the information we collect from and about you to provide the FNG Services and features to you, including: to measure and improve those FNG Services and features; to improve your experience with both online and off-line FNG Services by delivering content you will find relevant and interesting, including advertising and marketing messages; to allow you to comment on content, and participate in online games, contests, or rewards programs; to provide you with customer support and to respond to inquiries. When the information collected from or about you does not identify you, we may use that information for any purpose or share it with third parties.

We may use the information we collect from and about you for these additional purposes:

**To allow service providers to assist us in providing and managing the FNG Services**. FNG may make your information available to certain third party service providers, such as contractors, agents or sponsors, who help us manage or provide the FNG Services.

**To allow social sharing functionality**. If you log in with or connect a social media service account with FNG Services, we may share your user name, picture, and likes, as well as your activities and comments with other users of that FNG Service and with your friends associated with your social media service. We may also share the same information with the social media service provider. By logging in with or connecting a FNG Service account with a social media service, you are authorizing us to share information we collect from and about you with the social media service provider, other users and your friends and you understand that the social media service’s use of the shared information will be governed by the social media service’s privacy policy. If you do not want your personal information shared in this way, please do not connect your social media service account with a FNG Service account and do not participate in social sharing on FNG Services.

**To Deliver Video Content.** In the ordinary course of our business, we may share information that we collect from or about you with third parties in order to process your requests and fulfill your orders for video content offered through the FNG Services.  For example, to process your request to view certain authenticated video content through the FNG Services, we may need to share information about you with your designated television content provider and/or our third party service providers in order to authenticate and/or authorize you to view authenticated and/or localized video content through the FNG Services.

**To provide co-branded services and features**. We may offer co-branded services or features, such as contests, sweepstakes or other promotions together with a third party (“ **Co-Branded Services** “). These Co-Branded Services may be hosted on FNG Services or on the third party’s service. By virtue of these relationships, we may share all items of the information you submit in connection with the Co-Branded Service in an electronic form or otherwise with the third party. The third party’s use of your information will be governed by the third party’s privacy policy. We will advise you when this is occurring or obtain your express consent to share your personal information in these circumstances.

**To deliver relevant advertisements**. FNG and our service providers may use and disclose the information we collect from and about you to deliver relevant ads to you when you use the FNG Services or another service where you have consented to us doing so or where it is otherwise permitted by law. As noted above, third-party advertising networks and advertisers may use cookies and similar technologies to collect and track information such as demographic information, inferred interests, aggregated information, and activity to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interests. To find out more about third-party advertising networks and similar entities that use these technologies, see [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/), and to opt-out of such advertising networks’ and services’ advertising practices, go to [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).

We may deliver relevant ads to you by a range of methods including mail, telephone, email or SMS. You can unsubscribe from this direct marketing, or change your contact preferences by contacting us (see section 5 of this Privacy Policy).

**To contact you**. FNG may periodically send promotional materials or notifications related to the FNG Services. If you want to stop receiving promotional materials, follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. There are certain service notification emails that you may not opt-out of, such as notifications of changes to the FNG Services or policies. If you have installed a mobile app and you wish to stop receiving push notifications, you can change the settings either on your mobile device or through the app.

**To share with our Company Affiliates**. FNG may share your information with its related companies both in and outside of Singapore, including in particular but without limitation in the United States of America and in Hong Kong. A link to a website that lists Company Affiliates can be found at the beginning of this policy. Users who visit Company Affiliates’ services should still refer to their separate privacy policies, which may differ in some respects from this Privacy Policy. Where we share your information with Company Affiliates, they may use your information in the same way as we can under this Privacy Policy.

**To share with business partners**. FNG may share all items of your information in an electronic form or otherwise, with business partners to permit them to send you marketing communications consistent with your choices.

**To protect the rights of FNG and others**. There may be instances when FNG may disclose your information, including situations where FNG has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: (i) protect, enforce, or defend the legal rights, privacy, safety, or property of FNG, our Company Affiliates or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements and our terms of use); (ii) protect the safety, privacy, and security of users of the FNG Services or members of the public; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; (iv) comply with the law or legal process; or (v) respond to requests from public and government authorities, in compliance with applicable laws and regulations.

**To complete a merger or sale of assets.** If FNG sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, FNG may transfer your information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

**USE AND DISCLOSURE**

We may use or disclose your personal information for the purposes for which we collected it (and related purposes which would be reasonably expected by you), for other purposes to which you have consented and as otherwise authorized or required by law.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties in connection with the purposes described in Section 3 above.

Where we disclose your personal information to third parties we will use reasonable commercial efforts to ensure that such third parties only use your personal information as reasonably required for the purpose we disclosed it to them and in a manner consistent with the Privacy Principles under the PDPA, e.g. by (where commercially practical) including suitable privacy and confidentiality clauses in our agreements with a third party service provider to which we disclose your personal information.

  1. **SECURITY**

FNG uses commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. However, no one can guarantee the complete safety of your information. Except to the extent liability cannot be excluded due to the operation of statute, we exclude all liability (including in negligence) for the consequences of any unauthorised access to, disclosure of, misuse of or loss or corruption of your personal information. Nothing in this Privacy Policy restricts, excludes or modifies or purports to restrict, exclude or modify any statutory consumer rights under any applicable law. Please notify us immediately if you become aware of any breach of security.

  1. **USER ACCESS AND CONTROL**

If you would like to access, review, correct, update, suppress, or otherwise limit our use of your personal information, you may contact us as outlined in Section 7. In your request, please include your email address, name, address, and telephone number and specify clearly what information you would like to access, change, update, or suppress. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable.

You may request that we not share your personal information on a going-forward basis with Company Affiliates or unaffiliated third parties for any purposes by contacting us at http://foxsportsasia.com/contact-us/, with “FNG Singapore: Disclosure Opt-out” in the subject line. Please include your full name, email address, postal address and the relevant FNG Service in the body of your message. We will try to comply with your request(s) as soon as reasonably practicable.

  1. **OTHER IMPORTANT INFORMATION**

**Updates to Privacy Policy**. FNG may modify this Privacy Policy. Please look at the Effective Date at the top of this Privacy Policy to see when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the FNG Services.

**Overseas Disclosure and Location of Data**. The FNG Services are hosted in Singapore. Your personal information may be stored and processed in any country where we have facilities or in which we engage service providers, and by using the FNG Services you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside of your country of residence, including the United States of America and Hong Kong, which may have different data protection rules than those of your country. This includes the use of cookies and other tracking technologies as described above. As a result, please read this Privacy Policy with care.

Except in some cases where we may rely on an exception under the PDPA, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that such overseas recipients do not breach the Privacy Principles in the PDPA in relation to such information.

**Linked Services**. The FNG Services may also be linked to sites operated by unaffiliated companies, and may carry advertisements or offer content, functionality, games, newsletters, contests or sweepstakes, or applications developed and maintained by unaffiliated companies. FNG is not responsible for the privacy practices of unaffiliated companies, and once you leave the FNG Services or click an advertisement you should check the applicable privacy policy of the other service.

In addition, FNG is not responsible for the privacy or data security practices of other organizations, such as Facebook, Tumblr, Twitter, Apple, Google, Microsoft or any other app developer, app provider, social media platform provider, operating system provider, wireless service provider, or device manufacturer, including in connection with any information you disclose to other organizations through or in connection with the FNG Services.

**Collection of Personal Financial Information by a Payment Service**. In some cases, we may use an unaffiliated payment service to allow you to purchase a product or make payments (“ **Payment Service** “). If you wish to purchase a product or make a payment using a Payment Service, you will be directed to a Payment Service webpage. Any information that you provide to a Payment Service will be subject to the applicable Payment Service’s privacy policy, rather than this Privacy Policy. We have no control over, and are not responsible for, any Payment Service’s use of information collected through any Payment Service.

**Data Retention**. We will retain your information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or allowed by law.

Remember that even after you cancel your account, copies of some information from your account may remain viewable in some circumstances where, for example, you have shared information with social media or other services. Because of the nature of caching technology, your account may not be instantly inaccessible to others. We may also retain backup information related to your account on our servers for some time after cancelation for fraud detection or to comply with applicable law or our internal security policies. It is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information due to technical constraints, contractual, financial or legal requirements.

**Sensitive Information**. We ask that you not send us, and you not disclose, any sensitive personal information (such as social security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, criminal background or trade union membership) on or through the FNG Services or otherwise.

  1. **CONTACT DETAILS AND COMPLAINTS HANDLING**

If you have questions, comments or complaints about our collection, use or disclosure of personal information, or if you believe that we have not complied with this Privacy Policy or the PDPA, please contact us via:

http://foxsportsasia.com/contact-us/ 

Mail: Business and Legal Affairs Department, FOX Networks Group Singapore Pte. Ltd., 1 Fusionopolis Link, #03-01 Nexus @ One-North, Singapore 138542. FNG will take any privacy complaint seriously and any complaint will be assessed by an appropriate person with the aim of resolving any issue in a timely and efficient manner. We request that you cooperate with us during this process and provide us with any relevant information that we may need.
